showsite.us 2015-12-06

# show site information- showsite.us

Privacy Policy for Showsite.us

At Showsite.us, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us.   
This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Showsite.us and how it is used.

Log Files

Like many other Web sites, Showsite.us makes use of log files.   
The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser,   
Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends,   
administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information.   
IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons

Showsite.us does not use cookies.

Google Adsense 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Showsite.us send directly to your browsers.   
They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by   
the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
Showsite.us has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as   
for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Showsite.us's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of,   
such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.   
More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please to contact us.
